pdproxy.com 2019-11-15

# Privacy Policy

PD-Proxy VPN is committed in providing a safe and secure web experience. We are dedicated to safeguarding all personal information collected online and to helping our users learn how to exercise control over personal information while exploring the Internet. To help ensure a rewarding online experience for all users, we provide this summary of our information practices. This privacy notice governs the collection and use of information at www.pdproxy.com. 

As we continue to offer different types of content and services, we may modify our practices from time to time. However, we will treat all personal information we collect in accordance with the privacy notice in effect at the time the information is collected. 

**The Information We Collect**

www.PDPROXY.com may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. www.PDPROXY.com may also collect information about how Users use our Web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Web site or the domains from which Users originate. We may use "cookies" to track how Users use our Web site. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the Users' PC and use to identify the User should they visit the Web site again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our Web site.

**How We Use Information**

www.PDPROXY.com will use personally identifiable information collected through our Web site to contact Users regarding products and services offered by www.PDPROXY.com, we however will NOT share this information with trusted affiliates, independent contractors, business partners or outside entities.

**Maintenance of Information**

Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry standard security measures. However, we cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure. 

### COOKIES

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on our web site. However, we do not and will not use cookies to collect private information from any user which they did not intentionally submit to us other than as stated in this Privacy Policy. We use both "session ID cookies" and "persistent cookies." We use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Note also that registered users may optionally use a cookie to remember their log in details in order to automatically log in to our website. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your web browsers "help" file. However, please note that, if you reject cookies or disable cookies in your web browser, you may not be able to participate actively in forums, polling, shoutbox, and arcade. 

**THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISING**  
The ads appearing on this web site are delivered to users by our web advertising partners. Our web advertising partners may use cookies. Doing this allows the ad network to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. We do not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed on the computer of any user of our website by the third-party ad servers or ad networks. This privacy notice covers the use of cookies by PDPROXY.com only, and does not cover the use of cookies by any other party. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.   
We also use third party advertisements on www.PDPROXY.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

**DoubleClick DART cookies**  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google's DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx   
You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.   
Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. 

**LINKS**  
PDPROXY.com contains links to other web sites. These include links that are placed there by us (such as in advertisements), as well as by other registered users. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of any other website. We encourage our users to be aware of when they leave our web site, and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by us through the PDPROXY.com website. 

### CONTACT US

If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding our privacy policy and/or practices, please contact us at admin [ at ] pdproxy.com. 

**Collection of Logs**

During our normal course of duties, we do not monitor, record or store logs for any single customers VPN activity. We will however record the following data: 

  1. Time, date and location vpn connection was made
  2. Duration of the vpn connection
  3. Bandwidth used during the connection

This information is regularly cycled within our servers. This information enables PD-Proxy VPN to enforce our Terms of Service, spam, crimes using the service, etc. If there is a violation we will use these trace logs to determine which account is in violation. After lengthy analysis of this data, we will terminate the service and/or take further action.
